Curriculum vitae



Mohammad Amir Jamali

mohammadamirjamali2020@gmail.com

Mashhad, Iran 🔾

21 September, 1991 mm

GitHub 🕥

LinkedIn in

Blog ...

I have a Master's degree in Information Technology Management- E-Commerce, as well as, <u>a proven track record in several programming languages</u>. Additionally, I have extensive experience in launching and managing new startups. Along with programming, I am particularly fond of studying Machine Learning and Quantum Computing(QML).

EXPERTISE

- Machine Learning (Neural Networks and other Machine Learning techniques)
- Microsoft Certified IT Professional (MCITP 2008)
- Programming Languages:
 - > **JS**: JavaScript, Node, React, AJAX, NextJs, Express, Redux, Socket.io (MERN Stack)
 - > PHP: WordPress Theme and Plugins Customization (Woocommerce, Stripe Connect, WC Vendor, Redis, Elastic Search, Creating Gutenberg Blocks, Elementor, WP CLI...),
 - > Python: Web scraping (Scrapy, Selenium), Django (DRF, Redis, Celery, PyTest, Locust, Silk, Postgrsql), Cirq(Quantum Computing), TensorFlow
 - ➤ **MQL** (c++): Expert Advisor programing

RESEARCHES

- An introduction to Quantum Computing; Advantages and challenges (6th National Conference on Distributed Computing and Big Data Processing) 2021
- Comparison of the local generalization error model (LG Trader) with the exponential moving average (EMA) in selecting stocks with the highest return rate 2019 (Fourth National Conference on Applied Research in Electrical Engineering, Mechanics, Computer and Information Technology.)
- Predicting Bitcoin price with Bayesian Neural Network by using COT weekly report(Master's thesis) 2019

EDUCATION

Master's in Information Technology E-Commerce Islamic Azad University, Birjand branch 09/2017 - 11/2019

Bachelor's in Industrial Engineering

Payam Noor University, Birjand branch 11/2009 - 02/2014

SELECTED HONORS AND AWARDS

- Involved in finalists of UCL Hatchery Social Enterprise Award with Enviroble.Ltd (Santander Awards 2022)
- Ranked as the second-highest GPA among MSc students in the Computer Science faculty, with a GPA of 3.88/4.

WORK EXPERIENCE

О СТО

Enviroble.com

University College London BaseKX

03/2021 - 11/2022

London-UK

Founder

cikit.ir

01/2020 - 02/2021

Mashhad-Iran

Founder

Class724.ir

Science and Technology Park of South Khorasan

05/2017 - 11/2019

Birjand-Iran

Partner

Daneshjooyar.com

Science and Technology Park of South Khorasan

10/2015 - 01/2017

Birjand-Iran

FAMILIAR WITH

AWS DevOps

Github Actions

System Design

Jenkins

Git / GitLab

Agile Methodologies

Travis-CI

MongoDB

Microservice Architecture

RabbitMQ

kubernetes

Cassandra

Terraform

Postgrsql

SKILLS

Collaborative

Flexibility

Studious

Positive Engagement

Initiative Driven

INTERESTS

Music

Workout

Travel

Environmental Activities

Technology

LANGUAGES

English Professional Arabic Native

Farsi Native